Eloise at the Plaza is a comedy, family, mystery film directed by Kevin Lima.
Eloise is a precocious but lovable six-year-old girl
who lives in New York's Plaza Hotel.
Her caretaker "Nanny" watches over her while her mom is away.
Then one day, while trying to figure out how to get invited to a fancy ball as well as
how to meet a visiting prince, Eloise makes a new friend around her age!
So she decides to take him on a tour of the city - and all while
plotting some matchmaking hijinks for her other friends too!
Eloise, played by Sofia Vassilieva.
Leon, played by Kintaro Akiyama.
Nanny, played by Julie Andrews.
Sir Wilkes, played by Kenneth Welsh.
Mr. Salomone the Manager, played by Jeffrey Tambor.
Miss Thompson the Main Desk Attendant, played by Tannis Burnett.
Eloise at the Plaza is a 2003 American comedy television film based on the Eloise series of
children's books written by Kay Thompson and illustrated by Hilary Knight.
It stars Sofia Vassilieva as Eloise, a mischievous six-year-old girl who lives
in the penthouse at the top of the Plaza Hotel in New York City.
Julie Andrews, Jeffrey Tambor, Kenneth Welsh, Debra
Monk, and Christine Baranski also star.
The film was directed by Kevin Lima, written by Janet Brownell, and produced by
HandMade Films and DiNovi Pictures for Walt Disney Television.
Filming took place in Toronto and New York City.
It aired on ABC on April 27, 2003, as an episode
of The Wonderful World of Disney.
A sequel, Eloise at Christmastime, aired that November.
The film explores themes of hotel, new york city, nanny, prince, little girl.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.